你一会儿能帮我熨下我的制服吗?
Hey, will you steam my uniform next?
额
Yeah
有意思
Interesting.
还记得当初我问你
Do you recall this coversation?
Leonard  想要AA制买个熨斗吗?
"Leonard, want to go halfsies on a steamer?"
不  Sheldon  我们不需要熨斗
"No, Sheldon, we don't need a steamer."
你这是自取其辱
Looks like that rumpled chicken's come home to roost.
Hi
Hi.
这是你要的化妆棉
Here are the make-up sponges you asked for.
谢谢  我以为我还有很多
Oh, thanks, I thought I had more.
坑爹呢  你的化妆品比我还多
Damn, you've got more makeup than I do.
质量还比我的好
You've got better makeup than I do.
我要借你这个
Yeah, I'm borrowing this.
哎哎哎
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
这是我参加动漫大会用的化妆品
This is my Comic-Con makeup.
我爱你  但是有些东西
I love you, but there are some things
一个男人是不能和他女朋友分享的
a man doesn't share with his girlfriend.
这个想法太明智了
That's a wise policy.
我曾借过我姐的化妆品
I once borrowed my sister's makeup
为参加一个化妆比赛
for a costume contest.
最后得了严重的红眼病
Got a terrible case of pinkeye.
幸运的是  我本就打算扮成僵尸
Yeah, but luckily, I was going as a zombie.
最后我得了第二名
I won second place.
我觉得你们才去了动漫大会啊
I feel like you guys just went to Comic-Con.
那是圣地亚哥动漫节大会
That was San Diego Comic-Con.
这次是Bakersfield动漫大会
This is Bakersfield Comic-Con.
这个更好吗?
Is that better?
这个规模小很多
Well, it's a lot smaller.
活动主要是关于漫画书的
It's more about the comic books.
原来的动漫大会就是这样
The way these conventions used to be
现在一个个弄得跟好莱坞电影节似的
before they went all Hollywood.
所以回答你的问题  不  它没有更好
So to answer your question, no, it's not better.
那你们干嘛要去?
Well, then why are you going?
这是有关漫画书的集体活动
It's a comic book convention.
就像匹萨或者粒子加速器
You know, it's like pizza or particle accelerators,
即使不太好的  也非常棒
even the stinky one's still pretty good.
好吧
All right.
你们玩开心
Well, you guys have fun.
星期天晚上我就回来了
I guess I'll see you Sunday night.
恩恩
Yeah. Okay.
哦  等一下
Oh, hang on a second.
拿着这个
Hold this.
你要用来干嘛?
What was that for?
要是有人不相信我  我就给他们看照片
To show people when they don't believe me.
太棒了
Oh, this is the best.
周二早上豪饮
You have booze with breakfast on a Tuesday,
你会有麻烦
you got a problem.
周末这么做的时候  就等于在吃早午餐
You do it on the weekend, you got brunch.
Sheldon不喜欢早午餐
Sheldon doesn't believe in brunch.
他不能忍
He can't stand being at a table
桌子上一个人吃着煎蛋卷
where one person's having an omelet
另一人却在吃三明治
and another person's having a sandwich.
他都不嫌累么
He's not exhausting at all.
Oh
Oh.
是Leonard
It's Leonard.
他说他们在去Bakersfield的路上
he says they're on the road and headed for Bakersfield
以非常"快"的速度
at "warp speed."
我可能是喝多了
Maybe it's the mimosa,
但我还是回个"好好笑"吧
but I'm gonna give the kid an LOL.
他们这么兴奋真是可爱
It's cute how excited they are.
你应该看看Howard
You should have seen Howard
为了这次大会他缝了一周制服
sewing his costume all week for the convention.
Howard什么时候学会缝东西了?
When did Howard learn to sew?
他小时候  每隔几个月
When he was a little boy, every couple months,
就得扔掉他妈妈的裤子
he would have to let his mom's pants out.
我完全不理解他们为什么要去参加这些
I don't even understand why they go to these conventions.
就是啊  他们四个在一个著名大学工作
I know. The four of them work at a major university.
人都非常聪明
They're all super smart.
怎么能这么沉迷于
How can they still be into something
这些12岁男孩的小玩意?
made for 12-year-olds?
我不介意
I don't mind it.
我觉得Howie是保持着内在的童心
I think Howie's just in touch with his inner child.
但当他穿着蝙蝠侠睡衣睡觉时
Although when he comes to bed in his Batman pajamas,
我有时觉得我都摸到了他内在的童心
sometimes it feels like I'm touching his inner child.
可能是因为他们小时候都被欺负过
It's probably because they were bullied growing up.
在一个他们无力还手的世界
In a world where you can't fight back,
超级英雄完成了他们的梦想
superheroes provide meaningful wish-fulfillment.
我有点过意不去了  我也欺负过别人
Now I feel bad for picking on all those kids.
但也不全是我的错
Although, in my defense,
如果Danny Biffle不想吃一嘴土
if Danny Biffle didn't want to eat a mouthful of dirt,
他来上学就不要戴着领结嘛
he shouldn't have shown up to school wearing a bow tie.
我一本漫画都没看过  你们呢?
I've never even read a comic book. You guys?
-额  -没有
-Uh-uh.  -No.
我觉得漫画是他们生命中
I mean, it's such an important
很重要的一部分
part of their lives.
也许我们应该尝试读读
Maybe we should try reading some.
认真的?
Seriously?
漫画店就离咱们不远
The comic book store isn't far from here.
这想法太! 好! 了!
That is an amazing idea.
我喝了几杯了?
Okay, how many of these have I had?
我觉得你应该打开GPS
I think you should turn on the GPS.
它开着呢
It is on.
但是路线规划语音提示没有打开
But the turn-by-turn voice option isn't on.
如果你打开路线规划语音提示的话
I know I'd feel more safe
我会更有安全感
if you turn on the turn-by-turn voice option.
我爱路线规划语音提示
I love the turn-by-turn voice option.
我们真的只走了10英里吗?
Has it really only been ten miles?
我开  但是你得闭嘴
I'm turning it on, but just to shut you up.
Leonard  向左转
Leonard, bear left and continue
沿着210公路一直开
on Interstate 210.
这家伙好懂行啊
Ooh, sounds like that fellow knows what he's talking about.
我要是你  我就好好听
I'd put on my listening ears if I were you.
你干了什么?
What did you do?
我在网上找到一个黑客
I found a hack online.
能帮忙把我录的MP3音频
I was able to upload MP3 recordings
上传到你的GPS上
of my voice to your GPS.
太酷了
That is so cool.
我反对  一点都不酷
Counterpoint, no, it's not.
继续在210号州际公路上
Continue on Interstate 210
行驶五英里
for five miles.
关于州际公路有个很有意思的事情哦
Here's an interesting fact about interstates.
是么?
Really?
嘘  他说了很有意思
Shh, he said it's interesting.
州际公路是根据以下规则编号的
Interstates are numbered as follows.
偶数号公路是东西向的
Even-numbered routes run east and west,
奇数号公路是
odd-numbered routes
南北向的
run north and south.
三位数的公路
Three-digit route numbers indicate bypasses
表示是支线
or spurs.
看啊  Leonard  前面有座桥
Look, Leonard, there's a bridge.
我们冲下去吧
Drive off it.
我们离Vazquez Rocks不是很远
You know, we're not that far from Vazquez Rocks.
而且"星际迷航"有很多场景就是在那里拍的
Oh, they shot a lot of Star Trek episodes out there.
我们这车上就有服装
We've got our costumes in the trunk.
我们去那里拍些照片吧
We could go there and have a little photo shoot.
好主意
Great idea.
我已经有两周没吃任何碳水化合物了
I haven't had a carbohydrate in two weeks.
我这性感的颧骨必须在我吃了椒盐卷饼
These cheekbones need to be in front of a camera
之前在照相机前留下倩影
before I eat a pretzel and they're gone.
好啊  听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds fun.
哦  很赞哦
Oh, smashing.
但是  Leonard  你知道怎么过去吗?
Now, Leonard, do you know how to get there?
不知道
No.
幸运的是  车里的某人认识路哦
Yeah, well luckily, someone in the car does.
路线重新规划中
Recalculating.
在我们等的时候
While we're waiting,
你们知道是哪位总统签署了
do you know which president signed
高速公路法案的吗?
the Intestate Highway System Act into law?
答案在14英里后公布
The answer, coming up in 14 miles.
你们肯定都不知道
None of you will get it.
是艾森豪威尔 (美国第三十四任总统)
It's Eisenhower.
为什么他们都盯着我们看?
Why are they staring?
谁在乎这个?
Who cares?
尽情享受吧
Just soak it in.
帅哥们  你们好啊
Hello, boys.
哦  嘿
Oh, hey.
你们能不能别这么盯着了? 她们不就是女生嘛
Could you please stop staring? They're just girls.
和你们在电影或者图画里看到的没什么两样
It's nothing you haven't seen in movies or in drawings.
嘿  Stuart
Hey, Stuart.
什么风把你们给吹来了?
Wh-What brings you guys here?
我们想找些漫画看看
We were looking for a recommendation
你有什么好建议?
about comic books.
嗯  我建议你们不要
Oh, well, I recommend
开一个卖漫画书的店
you don't open a store and sell them.
其实我们只是想知道
No, we were just wondering
那些家伙们为什么对这些东西那么入迷
why the guys like this stuff so much,
所以我们也想看看
so we thought we'd give it a try.
好吧  你们对什么题材感兴趣?
Oh, okay. What do you think you might be into?
超级英雄  幻想类  漫画小说  日本漫画
Superhero, fantasy, graphic novels, manga--
你再这样我用水管喷你了！
I swear I will turn a hose on you.
一般他们都喜欢什么类型的漫画?
What kind of comics do the guys like?
什么都有啊
Um, a litt bit of everything.
多数是关于超级英雄的
Mostly superhero stuff.
好吧  哪个是最厉害的超级英雄?
All right, well, who's the best superhero?
嘘!
Shh!
你在这里不能问这类的问题
You can't ask a question like that in here.
他们会争得打起来的
Are you trying to start a rumble?
好吧  你有什么推荐的?
Well, what do you recommend?
嗯  我想想
Well, uh, let's see.
有正义的超级英雄
You've got your basic clean-cut good guys--
超人  蜘蛛侠  美国队长
Superman, Spider-Man, Captain America.
也有带点黑暗色彩的
Then you have your darker anti-heroes
蝙蝠侠  金刚狼  惩罚者
your Batman, your Wolverine, Punisher.
哦  坏孩子是我的菜
Ooh, I do love a bad boy.
所以你才找了位怕仓鼠的男朋友
As evidenced by your boyfriend and his fear of hamsters.
我要是你的话  我会选Fables第一季(成人童话)
If I were you, I'd go for Fables number one.
这个作品很有深度
The artwork is sophisticated,
很有智慧
it's intelligently written,
而且不会没有把女性物质化  也没有对女性的成见
and it doesn't objectify or stereotype women.
喔哦  Thor!（北欧神话中的雷神）
Ooh, Thor!
他真性感
He's hot.
嗯  算是吧
Yeah, he kind of is.
上妆中
And we're blending,
and we're blending,
搞定
and we're done.
我知道Data先生是不应该笑的
I know Mr. Data isn't supposed to smile,
但  我真心高兴啊
but here it comes.
过来  兄弟们
Come on, guys.
快来拍照
Let's do this.
是啊  我这秃头盖帽都快汗出翔了
Yeah, I'm sweating my bald cap off.
咱第一个pose该怎么摆?
So what's our first pose going to be?
我觉得我们得从星际迷航的经典打斗场景开拍
I say we begin with a classic Star Trek fight scene.
我来设倒计时
I'll set the timer.
Sheldon  你这算什么打斗姿势?
Sheldon, how is that a fight pose?
Data先生的武器就是他的大脑
Mr. Data's weapon is his mind.
我这是在操作呢
I'm wielding it.
打倒Borg!（Borg是W装扮的角色）
Phasers on the Borg!
霹雳娇娃
Charlie's Angels.
好的  下一个是什么?
Okay, what's next?
咱来拍几张
Now let's do
性感迷人魅惑的
some sexy glamour shots.
我来营造点气氛
I'll set the mood.
动次大次  动次大次  动次大次...
Oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz...
oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz...
动次大次  动次大次  动次大次...
oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz, oontz.
好的  酷毙了
Yeah, nice one.
动次大次  动次大次
Oontz, oontz, oontz.
就这样
That's right.
动次大次  动次大次
Oontz, oontz, oontz.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
Leonard  有人把你车偷走了!
Leonard, someone's stealing your car!
什么? 嘿! 嘿!
What? Hey, hey!
回来! 快住手!
Come back here! Stop!
偷窃是犯法的!
Stealing is against the law!
真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
我了个去
Son of a bitch.
我来报警
I'll call 911.
额...
Wha...
我的手机在我另一条裤子里
Oh, no, my phone is in my other pants.
-我也是  -我也是
-Oh, so is mine. -Mine, too.
还有啥办法么
Anybody got any ideas?
没有
Nope.
那现在我们只能归咎一下各人责任了
The only thing left to do now is assign blame.
都怪你
Nice going.
谁会在光天化日之下
What kind of a person steals another person's car
偷别人的车啊?
in broad daylight?
谁会把车钥匙留在车里呢?
What kind of person leaves his keys in the car?
我们不是都同意这是Koothrappali的错吗?
I thought we agreed this was all Koothrappali's fault.
你说的对
You're right.
都怪你
Nice going.
有车来了
Car.
大家都肿么了?
What is wrong with people?
为什么没人停车?
Why don't they stop?
没人停下或许是好事
Maybe we're better off.
万一我们上了疯子的车怎么办?
What if we were to get in a car with a crazy person?
Sheldon  看看我们吧
Look at us, Sheldon.
我们就是一群疯子
We're the crazy people.
或许我们应该举个牌子
Well, perhaps we should hold up a sign
告诉路过的司机我们没疯
that assures passing motorists of our mental competence.
好主意
Good idea.
你可以开始去弄了
Why don't you get started on that?
好了  我们就走走路吧
Come on, let's just start walking.
附近总会有加油站什么的吧
There's got to be a gas station or something nearby.
等下  你以为你穿的是队长的服装
Wait, you think just because you're wearing
我们就都得听你的了么?
a captain's uniform, you're in charge?
是啊
Yes.
好吧
All right.
好了  我看完了
Hmm, okay, I'm done.
你们怎么这么快就看完了?
How did you guys finish so fast?
不知道  大概因为里面超多图片
I don't know, there were a lot of pictures,
而且有一页只有一个词 "降雷吧! "
and one page only had the word "brakkadoom!"
好吧  反正我的街头智慧很强大
Yeah, well, I have street smarts.
你们觉得漫画怎么样?
So, what'd you guys think?
里面有很多动作
Well, there was a lot of action, Mmm.
故事情节轻快活泼
and the story moved along at a brisk pace.
总的来说...
It was, overall...
让我找个词来形容的话  就是...
what's the word I'm looking for?
-弱爆了?  -太弱了
-Stupid?  -So stupid.
我不明白为什么Leonard
I don't know how Leonard can get
那么喜欢漫画
so caught up in this.
太诡异了  他们能花好几小时
It's crazy; they spend hours
辩论这些根本不存在的东西
arguing about things that don't even exist.
真是浪费时间啊
What a waste of time. I know.
什么锤子能重到其他人都拿不起来呢? (漫画"雷神托尔"里雷神的武器)
A hammer so heavy that no one else can pick it up?
我觉得不是因为它重
I don't think it's heavy.
而是魔法什么的  所以只有雷神能举起它
It's some sort of magic, so only Thor can lift it.
这个就更扯了
That makes even less sense, I mean...
不  不  一点都不扯
No, no, no, it doesn't.
雷神是神
Thor is a god.
锤子是雷神的  只有他能使用它
The hammer is his; only he can use it.
就好像Sheldon和他的牙刷一样
It's like Sheldon and his toothbrush.
还有他那薄薄的诱人的嘴唇
Or his thin, beckoning lips.
等等  如果雷神的手正碰到锤子呢?
Okay, hang on, what if Thor's hand is on the hammer?
我的意思是  如果他用他的神力碰了锤子
I mean, if he's touching it with his god magic,
那是不是我也可以把锤子举起来了?
does that mean I could lift it?
-不是  -是
-No. -Yes.
到底是还是不是?
Well, which is it?
或许我们漏掉了什么
Maybe we missed something.
我们再看一遍吧
Let's read it again.
好吧
Okay. Yeah.
你要喝点茶么?
You want some tea?
好主意
Good idea.
我帮你一起泡茶
I'll help you.
等等  我们不是要看漫画么?
Wait, I thought we were reading.
是啊
We are.
我们只是...让你先看一会儿
We're just, uh, giving you a head start.
我真希望我妈在这
I wish my mom was here.
我们就可以都躲在她的影子里乘凉了
We could all hang out in her shadow.
穿着毛裤跋涉在沙漠中
Wool pants in the desert.
我觉得蛋蛋都要被煮熟了
I feel like I've got poached testicles.
可怜的孩纸
Oh, you poor thing;
你汗如雨下啊
you're sweating.
这总比车被偷好吧
That's so much worse than having your car stolen.
保险公司会赔给你钱买新车的
Insurance is gonna buy you a new car.
可没人给我的蛋蛋除汗臭
It's not gonna de-funk my junk.
童鞋们
Gentlemen,
表抱怨这么多
a little less bellyaching.
我们可是星舰战队的军官
We're Starfleet officers
博格集团的一员("星际迷航"里的高智慧团体)
and a member of the Borg Collective.
得了吧  Sheldon  我现在超没心情的
Please, Sheldon, I am so not in the mood.
Leonard  我们一生都梦想着
Leonard, all our lives we have dreamed
能身处一个我们热爱的
of finding ourselves
幻想中的世界
inside one of the fantasy worlds we love.
看  我们现在
And look at us.
不就是
At this moment, we are, in fact,
一队星际迷航的先头登陆部队
a Star Trek landing party
在外星世界陷入了困境  忍受严酷的环境折磨
stranded in an alien and unforgiving environment,
只能依靠我们自身的智慧  坚韧
relying only on our wits, our fortitude
和勇气坚持下去
and our moxie.
只要我们还拥有这些力量
As long as we have those things,
-就没有人能阻止我们...  -呆子!
-nothing can stop... -Nerds!
我恨这个星球
I hate this planet.
锤子上写着
It says right here on the hammer,
"无论谁握着这把锤子  只有配得上它的人
"Whoever holds this hammer, if he be worthy,
才会拥有雷神的力量"
shall possess the power of Thor."
等等  谁来决定一个人是不是配得上呢?
Hold on, who decides who's worthy?
锤子?
Does the hammer decide?
-是的  -不是
-Yes! -No!
锤子不能做决定的
It can't decide.
它是个锤子
It's a hammer.
可你说过它是个有魔力的锤子
You said it's a magic hammer.
是的  但是他还是不能做决定的
Yeah, it can't make decisions.
如果哈利波特的魔杖可以做决定
If Harry Potter's wand can make decisions,
为什么雷神的锤子不能做决定?
why can't Thor's hammer?
好吧  如果你要开始拿魔杖和锤子做比较的话
Okay, if you're going to start comparing wands and hammers,
我就没法和你认真说下去了
I can't even take you seriously.
大家好
Hello.
四杯水  谢谢
Uh, four glasses of water, please.
你们还要点什么不?
Anything for you guys?
能借用下你的电话吗?
Can I use your phone?
我们的车被偷了
Our car got stolen.
为什么不让Scotty把你传送出去?
(Beam me up Scotty: 星际迷航经典台词)
Why don't you ask Scotty to beam you up?
Scotty是第一部"星际迷航: 原初系列"里面的
Scotty was on the original series,
而我们是第二代
and we're Next Generation.
所以... 你们才好笑呢
So... joke's on you.
我们和他不是一起的
We're not with him.
在太空  你没法把东西拿"起来"
You can't pick something up in outer space.
那里就没有"起来"的概念
In space, there is no up.
哦是吗? 那为什么太阳每天都会升"起来"呢?
Oh, yeah? Then how does the sun come "up" every day?
还真是辩不过你的街头智慧啊
Hard to argue with those kind of street smarts.
Leonard和Sheldon在对门有整箱整箱的漫画
Leonard and Sheldon have boxes of comics across the hall.
为什么我们不找点看看?
Why don't we go look at those?
太棒了! 这就去! 看了你们就懂了
Oh, great! Yes! And then you will see.
我是对的  如果在太空的话
I am not wrong, because if we were in outer space,
人人都拿得动锤子
then anyone could pick up the hammer
因为在无重力环境中
because it would be floating around
锤子就自己飘在空中呢
in a weightless environment.
没错  笨鸟会用科学知识了
Yeah, that's right, the slow reader used science.
羡慕嫉妒恨去吧
Suck on that.
车上有什么贵重物品吗?
Was there anything valuable in the car?
我们的衣服  包包  手机
Our clothes, our wallets, phones.
还有大概价值300刀的化妆品
And about $300 worth of makeup,
所以现在小偷可能会伪装成任何人
so this thief could look like anyone right now.
化妆品?
Makeup?
嗯
Sure.
我们打算去参加Bakersfield的动漫大会
Uh, we're going to the Comic-Con in Bakersfield.
那有个大型cosplay大赛
They have a big costume contest.
说出来怎么就感觉不酷了
It's cooler than it sounds.
没有啊  我听着可酷了
I don't know, sounds pretty cool.
真的很酷
I-It is.
不仅仅是漫画书
It's not just comic books.
还有走来走去的卡通人物和玩偶
They've got action figures, toys,
还有电子争霸战主题的舞会...
a Tron-themed dance party...
够了够了  他知道有多酷了
Okay, he gets how cool it is.
需要的信息我都记录好了
I think I have all I need here.
你们要给谁打个电话不?
You guys need me to call someone?
要不给你们老妈打个?
I'm guessing your moms?
谢了  我们自己能搞定
Thanks, but we've got it covered.
刚和我妈通了个电话
Okay, I just talked to my mom.
她给我们安排了一辆租车
She arranged for us to get a rental car.
太棒了
Great.
我们还来得及去动漫大会
We can still make it to Comic-Con.
开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding me?
折腾了这么久  我只想回家啊
After all we've been through, I just want to go home.
别介样嘛
Don't be like that.
Howard  你跟他说说
Come on, Howard, talk to him.
我赞同Leonard
I'm with Leonard.
我也不想玩了
I'm done.
好吧  那我们这是2比2
Fine, then I guess it's two against two.
那该怎么决定呢?
How do we decide?
其实  是3比1
Actually, it's three against one.
神马?!
What?!
那我们的使命怎么办?
What about the mission?
你说我们是真实版的先头登陆队啊
You said we were a real-life landing party.
但  我们不是啊
Yeah, well, we're not.
我们是意淫版的先锋登陆队
We're an imaginary landing party
路上被现实中的狗血洒满了头
who had real-life garbage thrown at us
还被现实中的路人当成了白痴
by real-life strangers who think we're idiots.
说句心里话
And to tell you the truth,
我开始觉得自己确实是个白痴了
I'm starting to feel like one.
我想回家了
I want to go home now.
好吧
Okay.
那我们可以从"企业租车公司"租辆车不?
Did we at least rent the car from Enterprise?
明白不? "企业号" (暗示"星际迷航：企业号")
Get it? Enterprise?
我勒个去  明明很好笑
Screw you. That's funny.
如果绿巨人把雷神托尔举起来
Well, what if the Hulk picked up Thor
而托尔又拿着一个锤子
while Thor is holding the hammer?
然后捏?
Yeah?
那么根据物体的传递性质
Then by the transitive property
绿巨人就把锤子举起来啦
of picking things up, Hulk picked up the hammer.
非也
No.
绿巨人是把雷神举起来  只有雷神是把锤子举起来
Hulk picked up Thor, Thor picked up the hammer.
等等
Okay, hang on.
假设我去酒吧  泡了一个帅哥
If I go to a bar and pick up a guy,
而那个帅哥又泡了个美眉  之后我们一起走了
and he picks up a girl, and then we all leave together,
请问我泡了这个美眉了吗?
did I pick up the girl?
真有此事吗?
Did that ever happen?
嘿  我们是在讨论我呢  还是在讨论雷神?
Hey, are we talking about me or are we talking about Thor?
我们以后死也不出门了
Well, I say that's the last time we ever go outside.
你们听我说
Look, right here.
红巨人举起了雷神的锤子
Red Hulk is picking up Thor's hammer
因为雷神碰到锤子啦
'cause Thor's touching it.
不  因为他们是在太空
No, it's because they're in space.
他只碰到皮带好么
He's really just touching the strap.
皮带就是锤子的一部分!
The strap is part of the hammer!
不是!
No, it's not!
他们真是在争论漫画情节吗?
Are they actually arguing about comic books?
不可能  这不科学
No, that can't be right.
说不定"雷神之锤"
Maybe "Thor's Hammer"
是指甲油的一种新颜色
is a new color of nail polish.
红巨人一定是值得举起锤子的人
Then Red Hulk must be worthy.
你怎么知道红巨人值得?
How could Red Hulk be worthy?
你又不认识他!
You don't know his life!
真相只有一个
There's only one logical explanation.
在沙漠的某个地方
Somewhere in the desert we crossed
我们穿越了...
into an alternate dimension...
在这个平行世界里 这些个女人
where the women in our lives
终于可以欣赏漫画书了
can finally appreciate great literature.
如果真有平行世界...
If it's an alternate dimension...
听起来是个先头登陆队的世界
sounds like a job for a landing party.
舰长  请指令!
Captain, what are your orders?
我们先搜查
I say we investigate.
等等
Wait.
可能是敌人
They might be hostile.
好吧  但记得别打开
Fine, but set them to stun.
如果我们把Penny蒸发了
If we vaporize Penny,
我可再也找不到这么漂亮的女朋友了
I'll never find a girlfriend that pretty again.
趣事:
Fun fact:
艾森豪威尔总统在病房里
President Eisenhower signed the Federal Aid Highway Act
签署了联邦政府助建公路条例
from his hospital room.
哇  太有趣了
Wow, that is interesting.
每天都学新知识
You learn something new every day.
小测试: 请说出四个未通州际公路
Say, can you name the four state capitols
州议会大厦
that are not served by the interstate system?
哇  又一个测试  太棒了!
Ooh, another quiz. Yes!